United University Professions (UUP); Records apap039
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of the President, 1971-1997; III; 35.20 cubic ft.
  - Projects/Subjects -- John M. Reilly [RESTRICTED], 1978 June-1993 October; 1987 June-1993 May; 5; 16.0 cubic ft.
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 January 25 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 31)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 January 30 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 32)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1990 January 29 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 33)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1992 January 28 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 34)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee on State Operations Budget [RESTRICTED], 1993 February 02 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 35)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate and Assembly Committees on Higher Education, Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 December 19 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 36)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Higher Education Committee on SUNY Admission Criteria [RESTRICTED], 1991 May 08 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 37)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Higher Education Committee [RESTRICTED], 1992 May 13 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 38)
    - Reilly Testimony-Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 May 12 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 39)
    - Reilly Statement-"Colleagues Still: A Statement on Elimination of Mandatory Retirement in Colleges and Universities", AFT Advisory Commission on Higher Education [RESTRICTED], 1992 March 11 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 40)
    - Reilly Statement-Differential Tuition for SUNY University Centers-Statement in Opposition [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 41)
    - Reilly Statement-Draft memo to State re: "Let's Have an Accounting" regarding cuts in the budget [RESTRICTED], 1991 December 06 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 42)
    - Reilly Statement-"Keepin' on Keepin' On: Updating a Sketch for the UUP Strategic Plan or 'The Long Haul' Revisited", presented at the Fall 1992 DA [RESTRICTED], 1992 September (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 43)
    - Reilly Statement-"The Long Haul: A Sketch for a UUP Strategic Plan for a Strong Union in a Comprehensive University", presented at Spring 1992 DA [RESTRICTED], 1992 May (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 44)
    - Reilly Statement-Sexual Harassment [RESTRICTED], 1993 May (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 45)
    - Reilly Statement-Tenure [RESTRICTED], 1993 May (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 46)
    - Release Time Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 47)
    - Research Regulations/Misconduct Guidelines (re: research in science) [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1988 July (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 48)
    - Research Regulations/Misconduct Guidelines (re: research in science) [RESTRICTED], 1989 July-1990 January (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 49)
    - Retirement [RESTRICTED], 1988 December; 1991 October-1992 January; 1993 May (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 50)
    - Retirement, Early (including incentive programs) [RESTRICTED], 1990 June-1991 August; 2 folders (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 51-52)
    - Retirement, Early (including incentive programs) [RESTRICTED], 1992 February-1992 October; 2 folders (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 53-54)
    - Retirement: Optional Retirement Program in SUNY-background materials (1963-1964) on establishment of [RESTRICTED], 1992 May (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 55)
    - Retirement: Optional Retirement Program, Temporary Task Force on/Suspension of State TIAA-CREF Contributions (folder 1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1993 May (Box III.5.11 (III-Office of the President), Folder 56)
    - Retirement: Optional Retirement Program, Temporary Task Force on/Suspension of State TIAA-CREF Contributions (folder 2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1993 May (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 1)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1991 May-1992 January (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 2)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 January-1992 February (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 3)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 February-1992 March (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 4)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1992 May (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 5)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 May-1992 August; 1993 January-1993 February (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 6)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs including meeting agendas, minutes, and handouts [RESTRICTED], 1992 May-1992 June (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 7)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs including meeting handouts [RESTRICTED], 1992 May-1992 June (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 8)
    - Retirement: TIAA-CREF [RESTRICTED], 1991 February-1993 February (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 9)
    - Retrenchments 1990-91 [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 10)
    - Retrenchments 1991-92 [RESTRICTED], 1990-1992 (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 11)
    - Safety and Health [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 12)
    - Safety and Health [RESTRICTED], 1988; 2 folders (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 13-14)
    - Safety and Health [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 15)
    - Safety and Health [RESTRICTED], 1989 August-1993 May (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 16)
    - Safety and Health in the Workplace-UUP compilation of background information [RESTRICTED], 1988 April (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 17)
    - SASU (Student Association of the State University) [RESTRICTED], 1989 December; 1993 January-1993 February (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 18)
    - SEFA (State Employee Federated Appeal)-1989 Campaign [RESTRICTED], 1989 December-1990 April (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 19)
    - SEFA (State Employee Federated Appeal)-1991 Campaign/Loaned Executive Program [RESTRICTED], 1991 February-1992 February; 2 folders (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 20-21)
    - SEFA (State Employee Federated Appeal)-1992 Campaign [RESTRICTED], 1992 February-1993 March (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 22)
    - Sexual Harassment [RESTRICTED], 1990 February-1993 May (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 23)
    - Solidarity-UUP South Africa Labor Support Fund [RESTRICTED], 1990 January (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 24)
    - Solidarity Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 November-1988 August (Box III.5.12 (III-Office of the President), Folder 25)
    - Solidarity Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 September-1993 May (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 1)
    - Student Recruitment and Retention Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 October-1990 May (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 2)
    - SUNY 5 Year Plans [RESTRICTED], 1980; 1989 (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 3)
    - SUNY 1985 Flex Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1985 July (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 4)
    - SUNY 1987-1988 Financial Plan [RESTRICTED], 1987 August (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 5)
    - "SUNY 2000" [RESTRICTED], 1991 August-1991 September (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 6)
    - SUNY Academic Recall Study [RESTRICTED], 1988 January-1990 June (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 7)
    - SUNY-Access [RESTRICTED], 1987 December-1991 December (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 8)
    - SUNY-Advocacy Plan [RESTRICTED], 1992 September (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 9)
    - SUNY-Affirmative Action [RESTRICTED], 1977-1990 (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 10)
    - SUNY-Affirmative Action [RESTRICTED], 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 11-12)
    - SUNY's Best Program [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1990 October; 1991 October-1992 July; 2 folders (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 13-14)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1987 November (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 15)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1988 January-1988 March (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 16)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1988 February-1988 September (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 17)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1988 October-1988 November (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 18)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1988 December (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 19)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1989 January-1989 February (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 20)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1989 February-1989 March (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 21)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1989 March-1989 June (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 22)
    - SUNY Budget-Board of Trustees [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 23)
    - SUNY Budget-Clippings, etc. (folder 1 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 24)
    - SUNY Budget-Clippings, etc. (folder 2 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June (Box III.5.13 (III-Office of the President), Folder 25)
    - SUNY Budget-Clippings, etc. (folder 3 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 1)
    - SUNY Budget-Clippings, etc. (folder 4 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 2)
    - SUNY Budget-Campus Questionnaires budget cut plans impact [RESTRICTED], 1989 January-1989 March; 2 folders (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 3-4)
    - SUNY Budget-Campaign (letter writing to legislators, etc) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June; 2 folders (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 5-6)
    - SUNY Budget Crisis [RESTRICTED], 1988 June-1988 December; 1989 October (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 7)
    - SUNY Budget-Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1989 May (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 8)
    - SUNY Budget-Mailings to Members [RESTRICTED], 1988 October-1989 March (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 9)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1989 July-1989 December (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 10)
    - SUNY Budget 90-91 [RESTRICTED], 1990 January-1990 March; 2 folders (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 11-12)
    - SUNY Budget 1990 [RESTRICTED], 1990 May (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 13)
    - SUNY Budget-Campus Budget Reports [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 14)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1991 July-1992 April (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 15)
    - SUNY-Buffalo Proposal [re: research group in education?] [RESTRICTED], 1988 June (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 16)
    - SUNY-Chancellor [RESTRICTED], 1990 December-1993 April (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 17)
    - SUNY Committee on Institutional Performance [RESTRICTED], 1988 January-1988 May (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 18)
    - SUNY-Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1992 March-1993 April (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 19)
    - SUNY Disability Program [RESTRICTED], 1985-1988 (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 20)
    - SUNY Faculty Senate [RESTRICTED], 1992 January (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 21)
    - SUNY-Faculty Utilization [RESTRICTED], 1991-1992 (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 22)
    - SUNY's Future: Expanding the Mission, Fulfilling the Promise, letters regarding [RESTRICTED], 1990 April-1990 May (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 23)
    - SUNY Hospital Restructuring [RESTRICTED], 1986 February-1991 September (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 24)
    - SUNY Hospital Restructuring [RESTRICTED], 1991-January 1992; 3 folders (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 25-27)
    - SUNY Hospital Restructuring/Hospital Employees Survey [RESTRICTED], 1991 January-1993 March (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 28)
    - SUNY Hospital Restructuring Workshop [RESTRICTED], 1993 April-1993 May (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 29)
    - SUNY Hospitals (folder 1 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 30)
    - SUNY Hospitals (folder 2 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box III.5.14 (III-Office of the President), Folder 31)
    - SUNY Hospitals (folder 3 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 1)
    - SUNY-Meeting with J. Burke (Provost) [RESTRICTED], 1993 May 4; 1993 April-1993 May (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 2)
    - SUNY Patent Policy [RESTRICTED], 1986 October-1988 September (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 3)
    - SUNY Productivity [RESTRICTED], 1993 February (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 4)
    - SUNY-State Revenue Shortfall [RESTRICTED], 1988 June (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 5)
    - SUNY-State Revenue Shortfall [RESTRICTED], 1988 June-1988 August (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 6)
    - SUNY-State Revenue Shortfall [RESTRICTED], 1988 August-1988 October (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 7)
    - SUNY Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1987 May-1987 June; 1989 March-1989 November (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 8)
    - SUNY Statistical Releases [RESTRICTED], 1987 December-1988 June (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 9)
    - SUNY Statistical Releases [RESTRICTED], 1988 June-1988 December (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 10)
    - SUNY Women's Conference [RESTRICTED], 1990 August-1990 November (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 11)
    - SUNY Workload [RESTRICTED], 1991 September-1992 July (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 12)
    - SUNYSAT [RESTRICTED], 1988 March-1988 August (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 13)
    - Teacher Centers [RESTRICTED], 1986-1988 (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 14)
    - TIAA-CREF [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1988 December; 3 folders (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 15-17)
    - TIAA-CREF [RESTRICTED], 1989 February-1990 December; 4 folders (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 18-21)
    - Tuition [RESTRICTED], 1990-1992 (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 22)
    - Undergraduate Education, Task Force on/Program Assessment (folder 1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1988 November (Box III.5.15 (III-Office of the President), Folder 23)
    - Undergraduate Education, Task Force on/Program Assessment (folder 2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1988 November (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 1)
    - University Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 September-1989 June (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 2)
    - University Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 June-1989 September (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 3)
    - University Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 September-1989 November (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 4)
    - University Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1990 March-1991 December (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 5)
    - University Development Committee [RESTRICTED], 1993 January-1993 March (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 6)
    - UUP Benefits-Aetna [RESTRICTED], 1986 September-1991 September (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 7)
    - UUP Benefits-CDPHP Crisis [RESTRICTED], 1991 September (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 8)
    - UUP Benefits-Empire Plan [RESTRICTED], 1989 December-1992 November (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 9)
    - UUP Benefits-Income Tax Guide [RESTRICTED], 1991 December (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 10)
    - UUP Benefits-Mental Health and Substance Abuse [RESTRICTED], 1991-1992 (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 11)
    - UUP Contract Ratification 1992-Chapter Visits [RESTRICTED], 1992 July-1992 August (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 12)
    - UUP Designees to Various Boards and Committees [RESTRICTED], 1990 November-1993 April (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 13)
    - UUP General/Miscellaneous Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1989 December-1992 July (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 14)
    - UUP Grant Proposal Approvals [RESTRICTED], 1988 June (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 15)
    - UUP Life Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1991 January-1992 July (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 16)
    - UUP Master Plan [RESTRICTED], 1988 December (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 17)
    - UUP Position-"The Unfinished University: A Story of Disinvestment at the State University of New York" [RESTRICTED], 1992 May (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 18)
    - UUP Public Relations [RESTRICTED], 1987 June-1993 March (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 19)
    - UUP Research Department [RESTRICTED], 1988 February-1989 May (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 20)
    - UUP Research Department [RESTRICTED], 1989 May-1990 September (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 21)
    - UUP Research Department (including materials re: disparity study) [RESTRICTED], 1991 February-1992 January (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 22)
    - UUP Research Department (including materials re: disparity study) [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1993 May (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 23)
    - UUP Research Department-Disparity [RESTRICTED], 1992 December-1993 March (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 24)
    - "UUP Says [RESTRICTED]No to Layoffs" Budget, 1991 January 31 (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 25)
    - UUP Support of Other Unions [RESTRICTED], 1988 July-1992 September (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 26)
    - UUP/SUNY International Programs Proposals [RESTRICTED], 1989 December-1990 January (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 27)
    - UUP Teleconference December 5, 1989 [on "SUNY's Future: Expanding the Mission, Fulfilling the Promise"] [RESTRICTED], 1989 August-1989 December; 2 folders (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 28-29)
    - Vice President for Academics [RESTRICTED], 1978 June-1989 November (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 30)
    - Vice President for Professionals [RESTRICTED], 1979 April-1986 August (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 31)
    - Vice President for Professionals [RESTRICTED], 1986 September-1989 February (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 32)
    - Vice President for Professionals [RESTRICTED], 1989 March-1989 September (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 33)
    - Vice President for Professionals [RESTRICTED], 1989 October-1990 April (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 34)
    - WAMC Radio Show/The Best of Our Knowledge [RESTRICTED], 1990 October-1993 October (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 35)
    - Workload/Faculty Utilization [RESTRICTED], 1990-1992 (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 36)
    - Workplace Literacy (Teamsters) [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box III.5.16 (III-Office of the President), Folder 37)
- Office of the Vice President for Professionals, 1985-1996; IIIA; 1.83 cubic ft.
  This subgroup includes only the records of substantive projects that affected members of the UUP bargaining unit as a whole and for which the Vice President for Professionals was primarily responsible rather than the individual working files of each Vice President for Professionals. Other documentation of the work of the Vice President for Professionals is included in the officers reports distributed at Delegate Assemblies and made part of the Delegate Assembly records included in Subgroup IV, Office of the Secretary, Series 2, and in the various subject and project files maintained by both the President and the Secretary.
  Arranged in two series.
  - Reclassification Project [RESTRICTED], 1985-1989; 1; 1.33 cubic ft.
    The 1982-1985 contract between the state and UUP provided for a study of the promotional opportunities for professional employees of the State University of New York. After the commissioned study was issued by consulting firm Arthur Young in May 1986, steps were taken to implement its recommendations. A Management Advisory Committee on Classification and Compensation (MACCC) was established by the State University and given the responsibility of adopting a structure of professional titles that would provide promotional opportunities for professional employees. UUP participated in a joint labor/management committee of the same name formed to provide input to the larger SUNY MACCC (which was made up of just SUNY representatives). The joint labor/management MACCC acted in an advisory capacity only.